He talks about this victimization.
Do you think there's validity in that concern?
No, it's gaslighting.
It's gaslighting.
And how come?
Because we learned about the Holocaust
of the Jewish people of Germany
for every year of my grade school.
We are now watching a genocide of Palestinians
solely grounded in a concept of victimhood of Israelis.
And somehow, and somehow, when Black people are saying,
hey, these laws, these institutionalized systems
that are still organized around not granting equal rights
and equal access to Black people
are preventing egalitarianism.
That's not being a victim.
That's actually being very action-oriented
and continuing to point out,
you will not get over on us.
The suggestion that if we just pretend like we're not Black
and like nobody's a color, then racism goes away
is actually just quiet racism
because there is still systems in place
that are supported by this.
And there are grandparents who taught their children
who are teaching their children.
And we're watching it every day.
These thugs coming out of U-Haul trucks
with their face covered,
holding up Confederate flags,
saying we will not be replaced.